HENRIQUE FREITAS SOUZA

UI/UX DESIGNER

PROFILE

Phone +55 011 95435-5406

E-mail henrique@henriquefreitas.com.br

Portfolio henriquefreitas.com.br

LinkedIn linkedin.com/in/henriquefreitassouza

Address Taboão da Serra, SP. Brazil

PITCH

For more than a year I'm proudly working with UI/ UX Design, researching and building prototypes for mobile and web solutions that delight users and clients. The delightful part of my work and designs

come from the secret sauce of data.

EXPERIENCE

Conversion Chef | UI/UX Designer 2016 - Now

I create and test hypotheses based on data collected through the CRO process, perform A/B tests and heuristic analysis, design information architectures and redesign websites.

- Learned the fundamentals of CRO
- First UI/UX professional at the company

Nestlé | Project Manager 2014 - 2015

Managed infrastructure projects and represented Brazil as cloud solutions coordinator. Implemented and managed the cloud security process; managed CAPEX execution.

- 3 projects delivered
- 15 cloud security controls applied

Addbiz | Full Stack Developer 2010 - 2013

Designed and created UIs and graphic assets for hotsites, banners and e-mail marketing campaigns for an e-commerce. Developed hotsites using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C#, PHP, MySQL and SQL Server.

- Learned much about many modern technologies
- Deployed hotsites for an e-commercd with 200.000+ users/month

EDUCATION

Designer | Gama Academy

2016

5 weeks course immersed in the startup ecossystem along with successfull CEOs and designers to learn the required soft and hard skills to work at startups.

- One of the 100 selected over 5412 candidates
- 3rd in the rank of best design students

Information Systems | FIAP

2012 - 2015

Bachelor's degree.